Henry Max

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT

- +447493934800
- HenryMax@gmail.com
- https://github.com/HenryMax
- m www.linkedin.com/in/HenryMax

PROFILE

Irish. 32 Years old. Based in London.

Having worked as a mechanical engineer for the past 8 years, I have embarked on a new journey as a full-stack developer.

After over 1 year of coding including graduating from Le

Wagon's Full-Stack Web Development bootcamp, I am ready to utilise my newfound skills to help your company succeed.

EDUCATION

Le Wagon London - Batch #697

Le Wagon Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp July 2021 - September 2021

BEng (Hons) Energy & Building Services Engineering

University of Ulster, Jordanstown Sept. 2010 - June 2014

SKILLS

PYTHON

RUBY

RUBY ON RAILS

0.0.P

DATABASES & ACTIVE RECORD

HTML / CSS / JS

HTTP & AJAX

GOOGLE CLOUD PLATFORM

PERSONAL PROJECTS

TRAVELLIST I WWW.TRAVELLIST.UK

A website for avid travellers to track destinations, plan their trips and store their memories for their destinations with dedicated photo albums. Please view at www.travellist.uk

WORKWISE | WWW.WORKWISE.LIVE

A collaborative online platform that assists companies to search for and purchase properties to suit their business needs. View our demo @ https://youtu.be/6KB72NU5j6A

EXPERIENCE

CONSULTANT - CHOICE OPTIONS LTD FEB 2022 - PRESENT

- Working as a consultant for start-up building a multivertical recommender app.
- Creating figma prototypes for user testing.

MECHANICAL ENGINEER & ENERGY ASSESSOR 2013 - 2020

- Lead engineer for numerous projects from concept to completion.
- . Detailed design & thermal analysis of proposals.
- Regular client liaison and leading meetings.

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Sports I have played rugby and gaelic football for most of my life and also enjoy watching professional sport.
- Music I listen to a wide range of music and I also play the drums.
- Charities I enjoy volunteering and fund-raising.